ebookkake.com 2017-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Ebookkake

Ebookkake does not share personal information with third-parties nor does store information is collected about your visit for use other than to analyze content performance through the use of cookies, which you can turn off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings. The owner is not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this blog on other Web sites or media without permission.

 **Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**

Ebookkake allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements and collect data when you visit our Web site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. These companies may also use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Ebookkake does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. The Company’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

This Privacy Notice was last modified Jun 25, 2017.
